Guide to the Art Poster File ca. 1890-1910 PR55-1
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Magazine and Journal Posters, 1
  - Lippincott's/ My Strange Patient (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0172)
  - Lippincott's/ My Strange Patient (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0173)
  - Lippincott's/ In Sight of the Goddess (Carqueville, William L. (1871-1946)), 1895/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0174)
  - Lippincott's/ The Old Silver Trail (Gould, J. J. Jr.), 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0175)
  - Lippincott's/ Mrs. Crichton's Creditor (Gould, J. J. Jr.), 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0176)
  - Lippincott's February/ Ground Swells (Gould, J. J. Jr.), 1896/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0177)
  - Lippincott's March/ A Whim and a Chance (Gould, J. J. Jr.), 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0178)
  - Lippincott's/ "Flotsam"/ "The Washingtons in Virginia (Gould, J. J. Jr.), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0179)
  - Lippincott's/ "Flotsam"/ "The Washingtons in Virginia (Gould, J. J. Jr.), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0180)
  - Lippincott's/ An Inspiring Sword (Gould, J. J. Jr.), 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0181)
  - Lippincott's/ From Clue to Climax (Gould, J. J. Jr.), 1896/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0182)
  - Lippincott's/ A Marital Liberty (Gould, J. J. Jr.), 1896/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0183)
  - McClure's/ For April/ The Author of "Trilby" (Shipley), 1895/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0184)
  - McClure's for August/ Rudyard Kipling a new Jungle Story/ Anthony Hope "The Princess of Zeuda" (Beardsley, Aubrey), 1895/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0185)
  - McClure's/ A New and Richly Illustrated Life of Abraham Lincoln / 300 Pictures/ The Only Early Portrait (hitherto unpublished). (Knapp-Linson, Corwin), 1895/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0186)
  - McClure's Magazine/ 15 cts./ 1.50 a year, 1896/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0187)
  - Roosevelt/ A Character Study/ The kind of president such a man must be/ By William Allen White/ The November McClure's (Morton, Max Ralston), 1898/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0188)
  - McClure's/ Abraham Lincoln/ 8 Portraits of Lincoln/ Stories by Robert Louis Stevenson/ Ian Maclaren/ Anthony Hope (Knapp-Linson, Corwin), 0000/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0189)
  - McClure's Magazine for May/ Rudyard Kipling "The Destroyers", 0000/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0190)
  - McClure's/ For December, 0000/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0191)
  - Outing for June/ Outfit for Tramping and Camping/ Trotting and Pacing/ Champions of 1894 (Kurtz), 1894/06/00? (Item PR-055-001-0192)
  - Outing/ Ma P'Tite Philomene/ Graeco = Roman Games in California (Kurtz), 1895/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0193)
  - Outing/ In the Mountains of Japan/ A Tiger Hunt/ Cycling in Jersey Pines (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1895/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0194)
  - Outing (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1895/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0195)
  - Outing/ The Cup of Champions of 1895 and Their Crews/ Paw Ducket's Coon Hunt, 1895/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0196)
  - Outing/ The Football Prospects/ More Hunting in New Brunswick, 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0197)
  - Outing/ Football of '95/ The International Athletic Match (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1895/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0198)
  - Outing/ vol. XXVII no. 3/ Merry Christmas 1895, 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0199)
  - Outing/ Winter Fishing/ Moose Hunting (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0200)
  - Outing/ Holiday Number, 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0201)
  - Outing, 1896/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0202)
  - Outing, 1896/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0203)
  - Outing/ Model Yachts (Bonte, George Willard (1873-?)), 1896/03/00? (Item PR-055-001-0204)
  - Outing/ April (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1896/04/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0205)
  - Outing (Carre, Jean), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0206)
  - Outing/ Special Bicycle Number, 1896/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0207)
  - Outing (Scotson-Clark, George Frederick (1873-?)), 1896/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0208)
  - Outing for July/ A Canoe Trip/ The Twenty-Raters/ Cycling in the Tyrol, 0000/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0209)
  - Outing/ Rowing at Poughkeepsie and Henley (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 0000/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0210)
  - Recreation/ 10 cents (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0211)
  - Recreation (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1896/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0212)
  - Recreation (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0213)
  - Recreation/ 10 Cents (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0214)
  - Recreation (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0215)
  - Recreation (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1896/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0216)
  - Recreation (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1896/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0217)
  - Recreation (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1896/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0218)
  - St. Nicholas/ St. Nicholas or your life (Kelley, John D.), 1895/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0219)
  - St. Nicholas/ The Ideal Magazine for Young Folks/ The Beautiful Christmas Number (Rhead, Louis John (1857-1926)), 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0220)
  - St. Nicholas/ The Midsummer Number (Hampe, Theodore), 1896/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0221)
  - St. Nicholas/ Christmas Number (Humphreys, Maud and Smith, F. Berkeley), 1896/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0222)
  - St. Nicholas/ Danny and the "Major"/ A Story of the Plains (Mayer, Hy.), 0000/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0223)
  - St. Nicholas for Young Folks conducted by Mary Mapes Dodge (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)), 0000/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0224)
  - Scribner's October, 1894/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0225)
  - Scribner's November, 1894/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0226)
  - Scribner's for January/ first of a series of articles by Robert Grant on "The Art of Living" entitled "The Income" (Gibson, Charles Dana (1867-1944)), 1895/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0227)
  - Scribner's for February/ Contains the Second of Robert Grant's Articles (illustrated by C. D. Gibson)/ on "The Art of Living"/ "The Dwelling" is it better to buy or rent? (Gibson, Charles Dana (1867-1944)), 1895/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0228)
  - Scribner's/ The Last Quarter Century in America (Kenyon, C.), 1895/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0229)
  - Scribner's April, 1895/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0230)
  - Mrs. Humphrey Ward/ Contributes a novelette entitled The Story of Bessie Costrell/ Scribner's Magazine, 1895/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0231)
  - Scribner's for June (Gibson, Charles Dana (1867-1944)), 1895/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0232)
  - The United States will Pay/ July Scribner's (Reevs, George M.), 1895/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0233)
  - Scribner's/ Fiction Number (McManus, Blanche (1870-after 1929)), 1895/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0234)
  - Charles Dana Gibson is one of the illustrators in this month's Scribner's (Kendall, William Sergeant), 1895/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0235)
  - October Scribner's/ "The Chines Must Go"/ Andrews' History (Reevs, George M.), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0236)
  - Scribner's For Christmas (Rhead, Louis John (1857-1926)), 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0237)
  - Scribner's Fiction Number (Low, Will H.), 1895/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0238)
  - Robert Blum's/ Great Decorative/ Painting/ in January Scribner's (Kendall, William Sergeant), 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0239)
  - Robert Blum's/ Great Decorative/ Painting/ in January Scribner's (Kendall, William Sergeant), 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0240)
  - Barrie's Sentimental Tommy in Scribner's, 1896/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0241)
  - March Scribner's/ Barrie's Sentimental Tommy, 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0242)
  - Scribner's/ The Olympic Games and their Revival (Mayer, Hy.), 1896/04/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0243)
  - Coney Island/ by Julian Ralph and Henry McCarter/ in July Scribner's (McCarter, Henry), 1896/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0244)
  - The Olympian Games/ Depicted by Correspondent and Artist of Scribner's (Knapp-Linson, Charles), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0245)
  - C. S. Reinhart is one of the illustrators in this month's Scribner's (Kendall, William Sergeant), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0246)
  - February Scribner's/ C. D. Gibson's 1st London with Pen and Pencil (Gibson, Charles Dana (1867-1944)), 1897/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0247)
  - Life at Harvard/ in May Scribner's, 1897/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0248)
  - Do you Understand the Eastern Question?/ Henry Norman State it Practically in/ Scribner's for June, 1897/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0249)
  - Scribner's July/ Life at Yale-Henry Howland '54 (Lowell, Orson), 1897/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0250)
  - Scribner's for January/ The Story of The Revolution/ By Henry Cabot Lodge (Ogden), 1898/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0251)
  - Ainslee's Magazine for July/ Six Excellent War Articles this Month, 1898/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0252)
  - Ainslee's Magazine/ Enlarged and Improved/ Rule, Columbia, Rule the Waves, 1898/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0253)
  - The American Wheelman/ All the News Time/ Price 10 cents (Searle, Charles E.), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0254)
  - The American Wheelman/ Read/ All the Cycling News (Searle, Charles E.), 1896/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0255)
  - The Arean for June, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0256)
  - Army and Navy Journal/ volume xxxv #39, 1898/00/00 (Saturday) (Item PR-055-001-0257)
  - Army and Navy Journal/ Illustrations of the Spanish Army, 1898/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0258)
  - Atlantic: December/ John Fiske's Old Virginia (Flagg, James Montgomery), 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0259)
  - The October Book Buyer/ Vierge the Illustrator/ Price 10 cents (Vierge, Daniel?/ Muric?), 1890/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0260)
  - Phil May in the February Book Buyer (May, Phil), 1894/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0261)
  - The July Book Buyer/ Summer Reading Number (Clark, Walter Appleton), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0262)
  - The Bostonian/ February (Pierce, E. S.), 1895/02/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0263)
  - Carson= Pirie Monthly/ Daintiest of the Magazines/ 2 cents on all newsstands/ Fiction Fashions Fabrics Dress and Decoration, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0264)
  - Carson= Pirie Monthly/ Mr. Washington of America/ Beginning with the January Number, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0265)
  - Carson = Pirie/ Monthly 2 c. on all News-Stands (Justice, B. Martin), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0266)
  - The Clack Book (Wagner, Rob), 1896/07/00-1897/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0267)
  - Read Clips and forget your Dinner (Eddy, Henry Brevoort), 1895/00/00-1896/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0268)
  - Clique, 0000/00/00 (Supplement) (Item PR-055-001-0269)
  - Clique/ This Poster Free with Clique/ For Sale Here. 10 cents., 1896/05/00 (Supplement ) (Item PR-055-001-0270)
  - Comfort/ vol. 8 #5/ The key to a Million and a Quarter Homes/ A March Maid, 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0271)
  - The Cricket/ The People's Comic Illustrated Weekly/ Lots of/ Fun for 2 cts. (Dirks, R.), 0000/00/00 (Sat and Sun) (Item PR-055-001-0272)
  - The Echo/ Chicago's Humorous and Artistic Fortnightly (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0273)
  - The Echo (Nankivell, Frank A.), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0274)
  - The Echo/ For Sale Here (Sloan, John), 1895/11/00* (Item PR-055-001-0275)
  - The Echo/ America's Foremost Pictorial Fortnightly is Now a New York Paper/ New York People Should Read It. (), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0276)
  - The April Ev'ry Month/ Best of 10 cent Magazines (Brill, George Reiter), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0277)
  - The April Ev'ry Month/ The Best 10c. On Earth Worth/ Contains Reflection by the Prophet (Brill, George Reiter), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0278)
  - Fashions, 1896/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0279)
  - Figaro Illustre/ Christmas Issue (Bac, F.), 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0280)
  - Gallery of Players/ no. 8/ Price 25 cents/ For Sale Here (), 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0281)
  - "Gameland"/ A Monthly Echo from the Woods, the Waters/ The Mountains and the Fields, 1896/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0282)
  - Godey's Magazine/ Woman's Number (Parkhurst), 1896/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0283)
  - Godey's Magazine/ June Number--Just Out/ 10 cents a copy/ one dollar a year (Fowler, Carlton C.), 1896/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0284)
  - Bicycle Road Maps in Harper's Round Table, 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0289)
  - Godey's for May/ 32 Full-Page Pictures of the War Ships of the United States Navy, 0000/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0285)
  - Harper's Bazar/ Easter A. D. 1896 (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0286)
  - Harper's Bazar/ A Weekly Journal of Fashion/ Devoted to Every Interest of Woman and the Home (McVickar, H.), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0287)
  - Bicycle Road Maps in Harper's Round Table, 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0288)
  - Harper's Round Table/ Interscholastic Sport, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0290)
  - Harper's Weekly/ Christmas 1899 (Bradley, William H. (1868-1962)?), 1899/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0291)
  - Harper's Weekly/ Our New Possessions, 1899/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0292)
  - Harper's Weekly/ "My Boy" (Kemble, Edward Windsor), 1910/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0293)
  - Harper's Weekly/ The Development of the Colombian Exposition (), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0294)
  - Harper's Weekly/ Out To-Day/ The Nation's Journal, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0295)
  - Harper's Weekly/ "Bright Skies in the West", 0000/01/29 (Item PR-055-001-0296)
  - The Horseman/ A Fifteen-Year-Old Campaigner!, 1896/03/05 (Item PR-055-001-0297)
  - The Illustrated American/ The Non Pareil of Weeklies/ A Constant Delight, 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0298)
  - Illustrated American/ Vol. XIX # 14, 1896/04/04 (Item PR-055-001-0299)
  - International/ Tales from Foreign Tongues, 0000/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0300)
  - The Inland Printer, Now Ready Vol. XVII No. 2 (Bird, Elisha Brown (1867-1943)), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0301)
  - The Inland Printer (Bird, Elisha Brown (1867-1943)), 1896/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0302)
  - Inland Printer (Hapgood, T. B., Jr.), 1896/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0303)
  - Inland Printer (Leyendecker, Joseph Christian (1874-1951)), 1897/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0304)
  - Jugend/ Muncher Illustrator. Wochen Schrift Fur Kunst + Leben (Von Zumbusch, Ludwig), 1897/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0305)
  - Kansas City Karnival Krewe/ KKK Trademark (Millet), 1896/10/05-1896/10/09 (Item PR-055-001-0306)
  - The Lark (Lundborg, Florence (1871-1949)), 1895/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0307)
  - Frank Leslie's Popular Monthly/ Torpedo and Torpedo Boats/ Naval Militia/ Commodore Dewey, 1898/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0308)
  - Frank Leslie's Popular Monthly/ "Cuba's Struggle for Liberty" by Fidel G. Pierra (Brill, George Reiter), 0000/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0309)
  - Frank Leslie's Popular Monthly/ "Cuba's Struggle for Liberty" by Fidel G. Pierra (Brill, George Reiter), 0000/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0310)
  - Frank Leslie's Popular Monthly/ Continuation of the Great Lee Articles in the March Number, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0311)
  - Frank Leslie's Popular Monthly/ Continuation of the Great Lee Articles, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0312)
  - Leslie's Weekly/ The "Maine" Disaster (Schell, F. Cresson), 1898/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0313)
  - Leslie's Weekly/ Your Country Calls You (Wright, R. M.), 1898/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0314)
  - Life/ Out Every Tuesday/ Leap Year (Blashfield, A. D.), 0000/02/00? (Item PR-055-001-0315)
  - Life Easter Number. Out Every Tuesday/ 10 cents a copy (Sotirion, G.?), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0316)
  - Life Easter Number. Out Every Tuesday/ 10 cents a copy (Sotirion, G.?), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0317)
  - The Looker-On/ Musical/ Dramatic/ Literary, 0000/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0318)
  - The Lotos/ A Monthly Magazine of Literature Art and Education, 1896/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0319)
  - The Lotos/ A Monthly Magazine of Literature Art and Education (Dow, Arthur Wesley (1857-1922)), 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0320)
  - The Lotos/ A Monthly Magazine of Literature Art and Education/ 15 cents (Dow, Arthur Wesley (1857-1922)), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0321)
    This item is housed in Oversize Folder
  - Metropolitan Magazine/ Duse, Artist and Woman/ Loie Fuller/ Cuba's Struggle for Liberty/ 10 cents (Potthast, Edward), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0322)
  - Metropolitan/ Napoleon's Love Affairs/ Price 10 cents (Potthast, Edward), 1896/07/00? (Item PR-055-001-0323)
  - Metropolitan/ Special Midsummer Number/ Napoleon's Love Affairs/ Models and Art/ Women Who Own Yachts/ Audrey Beardsley (), 1896/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0324)
  - Metropolitan/ A Magnificent Issue, 1896/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0325)
  - M'lle New York/ The New Fortnightly/ Ten Cents/ Here She Is Again (Fleming, Thomas), 1895/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0326)
  - M'lle New York/ The New Fortnightly/ These Posters for Sale Here/ Fifteen Cents (Fleming, Thomas), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0327)
  - M'lle New York/ The New Fortnightly (Fleming, Thomas), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0328)
  - M'lle New York/ The New Fortnightly/ Just Out (Powers, T. E.), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0329)
  - M'lle New York/ The Journalistic Orchid/ Price Ten Cents/ Every Fortnight (Nuneket, Clio Ninton), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0330)
  - Munsey/ Specimen Pages From Mid-Winter (Rossi, Louis), 1895/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0331)
  - The New Bohemian/ A Modern Monthly (Charpiot, Charles), 1895/00/00-1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0332)
  - The Nickel Magazine/ Special War Features, 0000/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0333)
  - Overland Monthly/ Hale mau mau/ Pele (Dixon, Lafayette Maynard), 1895/06/00 (Item PR-055-001-0334)
  - Overland/ For August (Dixon, Lafayette Maynard), 0000/08/00 (Item PR-055-001-0335)
  - The Pall Mall Magazine, vol. XV no. 63, 1898/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0336)
  - The Penny Magazine/ Sold Here/ 5 cts. (Reed, Ethel (1876-after 1900)), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0337)
  - The Penny Magazine (Reed, Ethel (1876-after 1900)), 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0338)
  - The Penny Magazine for June/ 5c a copy/ 50c a year/ 6 complete stories by prominent writers (), 1896/05/00 (In pencil verso) (Item PR-055-001-0339)
  - The Penny Magazine/ August/ Five Cents (Smith, Curtis), 1895/08/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0340)
  - Peterson Magazine, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0341)
  - Peterson Magazine (EEG? (initials or signature?)), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0342)
  - The Philistine/ Rudyard Kipling/ Francis Wilson/ Philip Becker Goetz/ Stephen Crane/ Elbert Hubbard/ William McIntash/ H. P. Taber/ Eugene R. White/ Celett Burgess (Collin, Dwight Ripley), 1895/07/00 or 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0343)
  - The Pocket Magazine (Edwards, George Wharton), 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0344)
  - The Poster (Bird, Elisha Brown (1867-1943)), 1895/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0345)
  - The Quarterly Illustrator/ Holiday Number vol. II/ no. 8 (Henke, A.), 1894/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0346)
  - Sarony's Living Pictures/ The Vase Bearer (Sarony, Napoleon), 1894/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0347)
  - Sarony's Living Pictures/ Eleven Beautiful Pictures for 25 cents/ Zonia (Sarony, Napoleon), 1895/01/00 (Item PR-055-001-0348)
  - Sarony's Sketch Book/ Number 5/ Judith (Sarony, Napoleon), 1895/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0349)
  - Sarony's Sketch Book/ Scene from Twelfth Night/ Number 6 (Sarony, Napoleon), 1895/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0350)
  - Sarony's Sketch Book/ Number 8/ Cupid Contemplating (Sarony, Napoleon), 1895/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0351)
  - 50th Anniversary Number/ Scientific American, 1896/08/07 (Item PR-055-001-0352)
  - Scientific American/ Army and Coast Defence Supplement/ Guns, Anchor and Fortifications, 1898/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0353)
  - Scientific American/ Special Navy Supplement/ The United States Battleship Oregon/ Battleship Indiana with 13-inch Guns Swung to Starboard, 1898/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0354)
  - The Standard Designer/ A Favorite Fashion Magazine, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0355)
  - The Standard Delineator/ The Leading Magazine of Fashion/ February Number, 0000/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0366)
  - The Standard Delineator/ The Leading Magazine of Fashion/ March Number, 0000/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0367)
  - Standard Delineator of Fashions/ 10 cents, 0000/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0368)
  - To Date/ "The Female Rebellion"/ Concluded in this Number (Barnes), 1895/11/15 (Item PR-055-001-0369)
  - To Date/ New Year Number/ 5 cents (Barnes), 1895/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0370)
  - To Date/ Semi Monthly/ 5 cents/ A New Un/ A Good Un/ Serio Comic (Lowry, H. S.), 1895/10/11 (Item PR-055-001-0371)
  - Town and Country/ For Sale Here (Bird, Elisha Brown (1867-1943)), 1896/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0372)
  - Truth Art Number/ The Queen of Publications/ A Great Art Gallery for a Dime/ vol. XIV-no. 408 (Wechsler), 1895/02/00 (Item PR-055-001-0373)
  - Truth/ 20 Pages--Illustrated in Colors (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0374)
  - Truth/ 20 Pages--Illustrated in Colors (Watson, Henry Sumner (1868-1933)), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0375)
  - Truth/ Brightest of Weeklie's/ Christmas (Moorhead, Irwin), 0000/12/00 (Item PR-055-001-0376)
  - 20th Century Cookery/ A Weekly Journal for Those who desire to live well and economically, 1896/04/09 (Item PR-055-001-0377)
  - Varieties/ July Number, 0000/07/00 (Item PR-055-001-0378)
  - The Verdict/ Vol. 1, No. 9/ Advantages of Life in New York/ The Coroner: I can see no external evidences of injury (Luks, George B.), 1899/02/13 (Item PR-055-001-0379)
  - The Verdict vol. 1 no. 10/ Why Don't you Give the Bird of Peace a Chance (Mirs), 1899/02/20 (Item PR-055-001-0380)
  - The Verdict/ vol. 1, no 13/ Roosevelt's Idea of Reorganization (Mirs), 1899/03/13 (Item PR-055-001-0381)
  - Wiener Mode/ Viertel = jahrlich (Munk, M.), 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0382)
  - The Woman Cyclist/ It's Made for Her/ Her Book (Lowenheim), 1896/05/00? (Item PR-055-001-0383)
  - The Young Ladies' Journal/ A New Album of Coloured Paris Fashions, 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0384)
  - The Young Ladies' Journal/ Early Spring Fashion Number/ With 11 Supplements (), 1896/03/00 (Item PR-055-001-0385)
  - The Young Ladies' Journal/ April Part/ Couloured Fashion and Fancy Work Supplements, 1896/04/00 (Item PR-055-001-0386)
  - The Young Ladies' Journal/ May Part/ A New Story entitled "The Chess-Board of Love.", 1896/05/00 (Item PR-055-001-0387)
  - The Young Ladies' Journal/ October Part/ A Couloured Album of the Latest Autumn Fashions for Ladies and Gentlemen, 1896/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0388)
- Series II: Book Posters, 2
  Series II contains 100 posters that date from 1890 to 1907. These posters advertise individual titles or several books from the same publisher. Publishing companies include Charles Scribner's Sons, Century Co., D. Appleton and Co., Dodd, Mead and Co., Harper and Bros., J.B. Lippincott Co., all of New York, and Lee and Shephard of Boston.
  Book Posters are filed alphabetically by book title. Each poster has been assigned an item number based on that arrangment. All the posters are housed in flat files by item number.
  Artists, where identified, are listed in parentheses after the book title.
  - About Paris/ By Richard Harding Davis (Penfield, Edward (1866-1925)), 1895/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0389)
  - Adventures at the South Pole/ Beyond the Ice/ Or In the Land of the Pigmies/ By Cornelieus Shea, 0000/00/00 (Item PR-055-001-0390)
  - All Over The World Library/ By Oliver Optic, 1893/00/00-1895/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0391)
  - Hans Anderson's Fairy Tales/ Illustrated With Over 100 Designs by Arthur J. Gaskin (Hurd, L. F.), 1895/10/00 (Item PR-055-001-0392)
  - The Apostles/ Their Lives and Letters/ by Dr. Cunningham Geikie (Lincoln, A. W. B.), 1895/11/00 (Item PR-055-001-0393)
  - Geo. P. Humphrey/ At the Sign of The "Old Book Man"/ Number 25 Exchange St. Rochester, New York (Stowell, M. Louise), 1896/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0394)
  - Ballads of Our Fore-Fathers (Halm, George R.), 1895/09/00 (Item PR-055-001-0395)
  - Because I Love You/ Love Poems for Sweetheart or Friend, 1894/00/00ca (Item PR-055-001-0396)